{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "10 + 35",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "100 / 20",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "9 * 8",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "28 - 7",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 45",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "65 / 5",
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "7 * 6",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "83 - 16",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 19",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "78 / 2",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "3 * 6",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "47 - 23",
      "answer": 24
    }
  ]
}